videogamecentral.com 2013-05-05

# Privacy Policy

**If you have questions about an order you have placed with us,[Click Here and Sign In](https://store-3b521.mybigcommerce.com/login.php) to your account then go to "view messages" to send an email and we will be able to assist you quickly.**

VideoGameCentral.com is committed to respecting the privacy and security of your personal information. We will never compromise either one. We truly value and appreciate each and every customer.

### Protecting Your Information

Safe & secure shopping is our #1 priority. We use a variety of security measures, including sophisticated encryption and authentication tools to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind heavily secured networks. We use Verisign, recognized as the world's leader in internet data security, to process orders. All credit card and personal information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases.

### Collecting Information

Unlike many websites, we do not gather information about how visitors use our website. You can visit any of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. You will remain completely anonymous unless you tell us who you are. We will only request information from you when you decide to place an order.

### Sharing Information

We do not sell, rent or lend your information to any outside parties...period. We assure you that we take this very seriously and make it our number one priority and guarantee to our customers. On rare occasions, when credit card fraud is involved we may share information with companies assisting in the investigation. This is done for the sole purpose of protecting our rights and the security of others. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

### Questions and Feedback

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.

### Copyright Information

All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons & images is the property of VideoGameCentral or its content suppliers and protected by United States and international copyright laws. The compilation of all content on this site is the exclusive property of VideoGameCentral and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws.

### Terms of Use

By accepting these Terms of Use through your use of the Site, you certify that you are 18 years of age or older. If you are under the age of 18 but at least 13 years of age you may use this Site only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by these Terms of Use. VideoGameCentral.com does not intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 may not use this Site other than for browsing, and parents or legal guardians may not agree to these Terms of Use on their behalf. If you are a parent or legal guardian agreeing to these Terms of Use for the benefit of a child between the ages of 13 and 18, be advised that you are fully responsible for his or her use of this Site, including all financial charges and legal liability that he or she may incur. If you do not agree to (or cannot comply with) any of these terms and conditions, do not use this Site. All billing and registration information provided must be truthful and accurate. Providing any untruthful or inaccurate information may constitute a breach of these Terms of Use. By confirming your purchase at the end of the checkout process, you agree to accept and pay for the item(s) requested.

Any dispute arising from the use of this site, or transaction with this site, is binding to the state of New York.

### Quantity Limits & Dealer Sales

VideoGameCentral.com reserves the right, at our sole discretion, to limit the quantity of items purchased per person, per household or per order. These restrictions may be applicable to orders placed by the same credit card and also to orders that use the same billing and/or shipping address. We will provide notification to the customer should such limits be applied to an existing order.

### Pricing Information

While VideoGameCentral.com strives to provide accurate product and pricing information, pricing or typographical errors may occur. VideoGameCentral.com cannot confirm the price of an item until after you order. In the event that an item is listed at an incorrect price or with incorrect information due to an error in pricing or product information, VideoGameCentral.com shall have the right, at our sole discretion, to refuse or cancel any orders placed for the item. In the event that an item is mispriced, VideoGameCentral.com may, at our discretion, either contact you for instructions or cancel your order and notify you of such cancellation.

### Mint Product Policy & Guarantee

VideoGameCentral.com prides itself on quality. All figures & toys we sell are guaranteed authentic and "Mint in Sealed Box". This means that the package or box may have minor wear but the toy inside is always guaranteed in mint condition, never touched or played with.

### Privacy Policy

Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
